identityguard.com 2017-01-17

# Privacy Policy - Identity Guard: Privacy Now

_Last Updated September 2016_

At Intersections Inc., protecting your identity and personal information about you is at the core of our mission. To help us accomplish this, we have implemented a comprehensive information privacy and security program. We want you to be fully informed about this program and we hope that you will review our privacy policy.

### WHO WE ARE

Intersections is a leading provider of identity protection services identity theft education services for consumers. We also provide companies with identity theft management and mitigation services for their consumer customers. [Learn more about us.](http://www.intersections.com/)

### WHO DOES OUR PRIVACY POLICY APPLY TO?

Our privacy policy applies to our current and existing online and offline consumer customers. In addition, this policy applies to each consumer who visits one of our websites, uses our mobile applications, or otherwise provides us with personal information, even if the consumer does not buy our products or services. This privacy policy does not apply, however, to products or services for which we have adopted a separate privacy policy, unless otherwise specified.

### WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU DO WE COLLECT?

The types of personal information that we collect about you depends upon the service or product that you purchase or the website that you access. We collect and retain information about your transactions with us. In order to provide our services and products to you, we may obtain, for example, your full name; your mailing address; your e-mail address, phone numbers, Social Security number, date of birth, credit card information or other account or payment information, as needed.  We also may collect location information depending upon which of our services and applications you use.  With your express authorization, we may also obtain your credit report from one or more of the national credit bureaus. In addition, we may obtain information about you from other third parties in connection with providing you with the products or services that you request and to help us better serve our customers. For example, we may obtain information about you from sources such as public record vendors, technology providers, the Internet and other sources.

### DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR VISIT TO OUR WEBSITES OR USE OF OUR MOBILE APPLICATIONS, INCLUDING USING COOKIES AND OTHER TECHNOLOGIES?

Even if you do not purchase any of our products or services, we retain, on a long-term basis, personally identifiable information about you if you volunteer information to us online or sign in online to one of our member areas. Doing so permits us to understand and accommodate your online preferences and manage your relationship with us.

We also use various technologies to collect and retain information about visits to our websites and use of our mobile applications. Our websites, for example, may use first and third party cookies. Cookies are small bits of computer code that we or third parties with whom we have a relationship may install on your computer when it accesses our websites. We also may use “web beacons” (also referred to as “pixel tags”, “clear gifs” or other terms) or similar technologies to collect information such as how long a visitor remains on a particular page.  Cookies make your visit to our websites and mobile applications easier and more convenient. We may use cookies for purposes such as to authenticate users, provide tailored content, to facilitate the display of advertisements, or to determine whether a visitor is unique or has viewed our site before. While most browsers are set to accept cookies by default, Web browsers typically also have features that permit you to refuse cookies or to alert you before accepting them. Your browser manufacturer has information on changing the default setting for your specific browser. Please understand that if you refuse to accept cookies from our websites, you may not be able to use some portions of our websites or our services.

Our websites and mobile applications also may use various technologies to collect information when someone visits our websites or uses our mobile applications. For example, as you browse one of our websites we may collect information about your visit, but not identifiers such as your name, phone number or e-mail address. Via Web server logs, for example, we may monitor statistics such as: the number of people that visit our site, the date and time of the visit, geographic location information about the visitor, which page(s) are visited on our site, from which domain our visitors come (e.g., aol.com, hotmail.com, etc.), and the type of Internet browsers people use to visit our site (e.g., Microsoft Internet Explorer, Safari (for Apple Computers), Mozilla Firefox, etc.). We also may use tools that allow us to monitor which links visitors are using, what content on our site is being viewed, or how a visitor is accessing content through our site. We also may use outsourcing programs, such as Google Analytics, to assist us in analyzing data to better understand traffic to our websites, to tailor our websites and for advertising purposes. If you would like to opt-out of Google Analytics, please visit <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/> for additional information and instructions from Google about how to do so. Another one of our service providers is Adobe Marketing Cloud, which collect and uses personally identifiable information about our customers in order to help us deliver personalized marketing content. You can opt-out the collection and use of such information by Adobe by going to [https://smetrics.identityguard.com/optout.html?locale=en_US&popup=true](https://smetrics.identityguard.com/optout.html?locale=en_US&popup=true).

We may use Google and other third-party advertising companies and advertising networks to serve ads and collect information when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, phone number or email address) about your visits to this and other websites over time in order to provide advertisements on this and other websites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. This information often is aggregate data or individual information that is tied to a browser or device rather than specific identifiers such as the visitor’s name and address; however, some of this information might be considered to be personally identifiable under some federal or state laws. If you would like more information about network advertising and to know your choices about not having this information used by third-party advertising companies, please visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.

With Google, for example, we use several Google offerings, including Display Advertising, Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, and Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting as part of our online advertising efforts. These tools do things such as facilitate the display of third party advertisements that may be of interest based on your online browsing history when you visit our site, as well as to facilitate the advertising of our offerings to you when you visit other websites. These Google tools also help us to better understand the effectiveness of our online advertising and understanding, on an aggregated basis, the demographics and interests of visitors to our website. For more information about how these Google advertising tools work, please visit: [https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2404395?hl=en&ref_topic=1631776&rd=1](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/2404395?hl=en&ref_topic=1631776&rd=1). In addition to the Google Analytics opt-out described in the preceding paragraph, Google also has a mechanism that allows individuals to customize their advertising preferences. For more information, please visit: <https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662856?hl=en>.

We also may use other third-party services, such as Heap and Hotjar, to assist us in analyzing the activity of visitors to our website(s) that rely on cookies and other technologies.  This may collect information such as whether you are a returning visitor, without collecting personally identifying information such as your name.  We also may use Heap and Hotjar technologies to record images of activity on public pages of our website(s), such as mouse scrolls, clicks and/or keystrokes.  We do not, however, record images using Heap or Hotjar inside the Identity Guard member center.    For information about Hotjar’s privacy practices and opt-out choices, please visit [www.hotjar.com/privacy](http://www.hotjar.com/privacy) and [www.hotjar.com/opt-out](http://www.hotjar.com/opt-out).

Some Internet browsers offer what often is referred to as “do not track” mechanisms for browser users to automatically signal privacy preferences to websites that they visit. Our site(s) do not currently respond to do-not-track-signals, but some of our service providers, such as Hotjar and Crazy Egg, honor these do not track preferences.  For additional information, please visit the opt-out links above.  You can exercise other choices available to you, including limiting the placement of cookies on your device using your browser’s cookie control features and other choices described in this privacy policy.

Finally, Intersections websites may include links to websites operated by third parties. We do not control the information, through cookies or otherwise, that those third parties may obtain from you if you follow links to visit their websites, nor do we control their use and sharing of that information.

### DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM OR ABOUT CHILDREN?

None of our products and services or websites are designed for use by minors under the age of 18. If you are under 18 years old, please do not submit any personal information to us.  We may collect information from our adult consumer customers about their children if relevant to the service being offered.

Parents and guardians of minors, for example, may be eligible to purchase our minor monitoring service. If you purchase the minor monitoring service, you must provide us with proof, satisfactory to us, that you are, in fact, the parent or legal guardian of the child in order to obtain information about a child through this service. Except to provide the minor monitoring service to enrolled customers, we do not intentionally obtain or retain information about minors.

If you are participating in the minor monitoring service, we do not share information about your child for any purposes, including marketing, except as expressly authorized by you or as set forth below:

  * We may share information about your child with our service providers to fulfill the minor monitoring service. Our service providers are required to comply with Intersections’ privacy policy.
  * We may share information about your child to protect against fraud or as otherwise permitted or required by law, including to protect our legal interests.

### HOW DO WE USE THE INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU?

We use personal information about you to verify your identity and to protect against fraud. We also use this information for our everyday business purposes, such as quality assurance and testing; to process your transactions; maintain your account; respond to court orders and legal investigations; or interact with our service providers. Further, we use your information to market our products and services to you and for joint marketing with other companies. We do not use your credit report information except as authorized by you or as required or permitted by law.

### WHAT INFORMATION ABOUT YOU DO WE SHARE?

We do not share personally identifiable information about you with nonaffiliated third parties, except as follows:

  * With our service providers that help us to provide our products and services to you (such as credit card processors, credit bureaus and other sources of information we include in our services, and firms that assist us with our mailings, marketing and related services).
  * In accordance with your express instructions or authorization.
  * If you enrolled in the service via a financial institution with which we have a joint marketing agreement, we also may disclose certain of your information to that financial institution solely for use in connection with our jointly offered products and services. A joint marketing agreement between Intersections and a nonaffiliated company is an agreement under which Intersections and our nonaffiliated marketing partner agree to market various products or services to you.
  * We may share personal information with companies affiliated with Intersections in cases where our affiliated company is providing services to Intersections. We do not, however, share personal information about you with our affiliated companies for their marketing purposes.
  * Finally, in addition to the purposes described above, we may share personally identifiable information about you with nonaffiliated third parties for fraud prevention or other non-marketing purposes as permitted or required by law.

### CAN YOU OPT-OUT OF OUR SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT YOU?

Financial companies, including Intersections, choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives you the right to limit some, but not all, sharing. We have already disclosed the circumstances under which we share your personal information. However, it is important for you to know that you may elect for us not to have us contact you for marketing purposes. You may call us or, if we send you an e-mail primarily for a marketing purpose, you may follow the instructions in the e-mail to opt out of receiving further marketing communications.

### HOW DO WE PROTECT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ABOUT YOU?

To protect personal information about you from unauthorized access or use, we permit access only to Intersections employees and employees of our service providers who have a need to know. In addition, we have implemented, and we maintain, technical, administrative and physical security safeguards.

### HOW DO WE CHANGE OUR PRIVACY POLICY?

We will not change our privacy policy unless those changes are first posted on our websites. If the change permits or requires any expanded sharing of personal information about you, we will send you a specific notice, either manually or online.

If Intersections is acquired by another company or business, or merges with another company or business, or enters into any similar business transaction, personal information about you may be transferred as a part of that transaction. We will post a notice of that transaction on our websites and/or send you a privacy notice, if required by law.

### QUESTIONS AND COMMENTS?

If you have questions or comments about our privacy policy, please contact us at the customer service number posted on our websites or provided in your materials.
